My name's Scott Allen and I own the Business Next Door,
Allen Landscape Center.
And I've been there for 40 years.
I also associated with Pepe's Restaurant
and Javier's been there 27 years.
Javier runs the cleanest restaurant I've ever seen.
My garden center is spotless
and ever since I got to know Ed, when he came out here four
or five years ago, I watched him take this place.
It was already okay,
but he really made the outside the inside clean
and put all the right stuff in here.
And he is very particular in
how the place looks and how clean it is.
And that carries over.
And I know this from personal experience
'cause I've had their company Ed
and the Phil Collision work on several of my vehicles
and I've recommended him to other people that come in.
And everyone's been totally satisfied.
There hasn't been a problem with what the work he's done
for me, but if there ever was a problem, all you have
to do is call him back up and he would straighten it out.
So I've been blessed to have a clean place
that I keep cleanest.
Garden Center around Pepe runs the cleanest restaurant
and this guy has matched us in the way he runs his business
in the cleanliness and the finished product.
If you'll be very happy if you hired him to do your work
and if you don't aren't happy, come see me
and I'll give it a call.